(Mr. Rostenkowski:)No, you may not.
Let me tell you something.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)When I first met you...
You just gonna stand there?
(Howard:)I'm sorry, I didn't know.
ls this going to?...
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)When I first met you, I didn't like you.
(Howard:)I'm aware of that, sir.
But then you and l
had some time together.
Uh-huh, heh.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)It did not get better.
Right, right, heh.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)That silly Beatle haircut.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)You riding around on a red Vespa.
And you're still living at home
with your mother.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)To be honest, I thought Bernadette
chose you to punish me.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)But then I heard
about your astronaut thing...
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)...and I realized I judged you too fast.
(Mr. Rostenkowski:)Maybe you are the right guy
for my little girl.
(Howard:)Oh, I am. And just so you know
l'd still be an astronaut...